According to the proximity of the joint points
Open the clothing of a transparent pot
Then select the transparent pot tool in the 2D or 3D window
You can see the blue transparent pot grid displayed in the window
In the video, we deliberately created the wrong transparent pot position
Right-click to reopen the menu
Then click all to reset the grid
The newly created panels will automatically be created on the top of the original panel
And maintain the original panel shape
Then select all panel outlines in the display settings in the 2D window
Click and drag the mouse
At this time, you can only select the panels to reset the grid
Move them to the point where they do not overlap with the original panel
If you want to reverse lock
You can go to the display settings
Unlock all panel outlines
Then click to lock all panels after resetting
At this time, you can only select the panels that were originally created
In the 3D window
Move them to the panels that do not overlap with the original panel
Find the folder window, click to undo
Then click OBJ
Then enter the folder name and click to save
When the OBJ is knocked out and opened
And select the point where they are close to each other
When selecting this option
A 3D window will appear at the bottom of it
The top of the merge will be shown as red, and the top of the merge that cannot be merged will be shown as blue.
Now let's take a look at the grid part that was left empty before.
Adjust the merge distance to a larger or smaller value.
The larger the gap, the greater the merge distance.
When the effect is satisfied, click on the bottom of the OBJ window to confirm that the grid will be merged.
Open the OBJ file in other 3D software, you can see that although there is no merge line, the top points of the edge of the panel are still combined.
The merge close to the top point function will also work on panels that have a merge line relationship and panels that do not have a merge line relationship.
The merge accounts for bothzech and the transverse triangle on projeto5.
Now, let's perform thewolfII modification.
Here, the merge doesn't give me a merge line.
And thanks to this, it does exist for the seemedance only.
But, this method is soon complete from scratch.